[Ardent Spirits Keg]
Main script from: Criminal Scans
Preview TL: Rohupt
[Ardent Spirits Keg]
Timing: Netflix JP
Styling/Typesetting/TLC: Merlot-kun
Beika Town! Beika Town!
Please watch your step when...
- No way!?
- This is Beika Town, y'know!?
- Do you have a death wish!?
‎- Get back in here immediately!
Ordinary folks don't even
come close to this town!
Please don't worry...
Because I'll be the one doing the killing!
Along came a culprit
That bastard is somewhere in this town.
I'll kill him! That's the reason I came here.
This ticket to Beika Town is...
A one-way ticket that leads to tragedy!
C'mon Ran!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Wait up, Sonoko!
You dropped this...
Thank you.
A suspicious person...
That's hardly surprising in this city.
Well then, once again,
the one-way ticket to tragedy...
There's no opening to put the ticket in!
Sir, the tickets go in through this gate.
T-there is?
That's so cute!
Hey, Sonoko, you shouldn't laugh.
But, but...
Don't blame me if you get killed.
Alright!
I don't have the luxury of murdering
someone over something so trivial.
You narrowly escaped death.
This is Beika Town!
The city of crimes that I admire!
The city I will live in starting today!
Their name is Hanzawa-san.
And they're the culprit
of a crime that's yet to happen!
Continues in Part B
First I need to find a place to stay!
I need to somehow find one at
a rent of no more than 50,000 yen...
‎Eh!? 32,000 yen!?
It has good natural lighting, a south-facing corner room,
it's just five years old, and even has separate toilets!
All of that for 32k!?
No, there has to be a catch.
Such property couldn't exist for real,
it must be a customer-luring tactic!
And then when you go say,
"I'd like to take a look at this"...
or something like that...
You see, this one's been rented already,
I just forgot to take down the ad.
At which point he'll go on to suggest
a more expensive apartment!
Well, if that's the case...
Welcome!
I'd like to ask about the apartment
advertised at 32,000 yen outside.
It is still available, right!?
It is.
I-It is?
Of course, it is.
The landlord is a nice person as well,
and there's neither deposit
nor key money to be paid!
To think that the initial cost
would be this low!?
An instant property visit.
Isn't this a bit strange?
‎No matter what, it's too cheap.
Maybe it's really filthy,
‎or there could be a graveyard in front!
Here we are.
A condominium!
Here you go.
Such a great room!
The scenery's also splendid!
Isn't it? The convenience store's nearby,
and it's only a three minute walk to the station!
This is the best!
Erm, this apartment...
Is there something wrong with it?
Isn't it a bit too cheap?
No, no, this is normal.
For an exceedingly normal...
Stigmatized property, that is!
Stigmatized property!
For example, it's in this spot that a golfer
struck and fatally wounded his
model girlfriend with a golf club!
Don't say that!
Here! There was a lot of blood in this spot!
Don't point at it!
I'll be planning that man's murder in
an apartment where an actual crime took place!
That's kinda scary!
I-I'd like to take a look at the
the other options too, please.
Really?
Inside a suitcase under
the bed in this apartment,
a corpse was found
in a tightly packed posture.
Don't say that!
This is a bathroom in which
a woman killed her younger sister.
There's no way I'll be able to shower in here!
And in here, as you can already see...
"Beika Real Estate"
Um...
Aren't there any apartments
which aren't stigmatized?
Yes, we do, but...
A 4.5-tatami single room apartment constructed
twenty years ago, wooden, and without a bathroom.
The rent's 150k yen, plus deposit
and key money worth 3 months each!
Isn't this extremely strange!?
I think you've got the wrong
end of the stick here...
What place do you think this is?
This is Beika Town!
Beika
Town
Beika Town!
Crime-free apartments are extremely rare here.
In the last twenty years, the number of
stigmatized properties has grown explosively.
Maybe it's a conspiracy of sorts,
‎or perhaps it's the work of a shinigami...
Those of little means are left with no choice
but to go with stigmatized property.
That is the reality of this city.
Listen up! I'm just giving
some friendly advice!
Go back to the countryside, youngling!
The apartment that we visited first,
I'd like to once more...
It really is a great apartment.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, but for stigmatized property,
don't you think that 32k's a bit too much?
No, no... I can't make it any cheaper than this.
Then, with this, rent should be reduced, right!?
Its value dropped.
So, what'll you do?
Ah, I'll have to think about it.
His new life is still out of reach.
Omake!
Omake
Where is he?
Where is he...
Beika Town really has a lot of people.
But somewhere in this city is that person.
No matter where he hides,
I'll definitely find him.
And kill him!
I saw Yoko-chan here the last day!
Eh!? That idol, Okino Yoko-chan?
Yup! She was shopping normally!
Really!?
See you later!
See you later...
I, Hanzawa, whose both body
and soul are pitch black,
from Izumo, Shimane Prefecture,
have come all the way to this town
which has the world's highest
crime rate – Beika Town!
That aside, I'm in big trouble all of a sudden!
I can't find a good apartment to lodge in!
No matter where I go,
the properties are stigmatized!
Just what the heck's up with this city!?
But, however! I got a hint from
the onigiri-faced brat who randomly passed by me!
So I came up with of a perfect plan!
From here on, I can freely live
my life of crime without having to hold back!
Next time, "Encountering people is such a mysterious thing"!
Encountering people is such a mysterious thing
And thanks for not being angry...
with the parodies being too overdone!
Don't miss it!